Your Majesty. The remains have arrived.
I was just conversing with Clovis actually.
Huh?
The project must proceed without a moment's delay.
{\fade(255,0,255,0,500,5500,8000)}Subtitle: Willing
Jibun wo sekai sae mo\N{\c&H00FF00&}The moment when I might be able...
Kaete shimae sou na shunkan wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To change myself and even the world
Itsumo sugu soba ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}It's always right there at my side
Kakusenu iradachi to\N{\c&H00FF00&}Even as I stood still,looking at myself
Tachitsukusu jibun wo mitsume\N{\c&H00FF00&}With undisguised frustration
Mayoi nagara nayami nagara\N{\c&H00FF00&}Feeling lost,feeling anguished
Kuyami nagara kimereba ii sa\N{\c&H00FF00&}Feeling mournful,deciding what to do
Kimi ga kureta kotoba hitotsu\N{\c&H00FF00&}All it took was a single word from you
Tomadoi wa kiesari\N{\c&H00FF00&}And my uncertainty vanished
Karappo datta boku no heya ni hikari ga sashita\N{\c&H00FF00&}You let the light shine into what was my empty room
Miageta oozora ga\N{\c&H00FF00&}The sky I had been looking up at...
Aoku sumikitte yuku\N{\c&H00FF00&}Cleared and turned blue
Tozashita madowo hiraku\N{\c&H00FF00&}And I decided to throw open...
Koto kimeta\N{\c&H00FF00&}The windows that were kept closed
Jibun wo sekai sae mo\N{\c&H00FF00&}The moment when I might be able...
Kaete shimae sou na shunkan wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To change myself and even the world
Kanjiru ima koko ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}I feel it right here with me
{\pos(960,900)\fs60\kf100\2a&HFF&}The Stolen Mask
What's an Eleven doing here?
He was a suspect in Prince Clovis' murder!
But the teacher says the charges were dropped.
He was suspicious enough to arrest,though. Right?
You don't really think he is a terrorist,do you?
Uh...
Of course he isn't.
The school board would know something like that.
An Eleven here at school?
He is an Honorary Britanian.
I know... but still all the same.
Well he doesn't look all that scary to me,
why don't we just talk to him? I'm sure he's totally...
Hey,the guy just got here. Give him some space.
Seven years since we used this signal. Long time,huh?
Meeting on the roof like the old days.
Yeah.
I'm glad you're okay. I've been worried.
Alive and kicking thanks to you.
You almost died trying to protect me.
I was just returning the favor from 7 years ago.
Uh.
Ah,what about that girl? You know,from the capsule.
I don't really know. We got separated during the fray.
But you would know more about her than I do,right?
No. The only ones who knew anything were the inner circle of the Royal Guard.
I see.
And your name. Do I still call you Lelouch?
The records count my old identity among the dead.
I go by the name Lelouch Lamperouge now.
Oh.
And you? What happened at your court-martial?
And why did you enroll at the school?
I'm as surprised as you are.
What are the odds that we'd end up at the same school?
Truth is,someone arranged for me to receive a proper investigation.
And that person said that a 17-year-old should be in school.
Were all of these painted by Clovis?
Yes.
Such gentle colors. Very much akin to my brother.
We've successfully identified the guerrillas.
That's good. Now all we need is their hide-out.
Get that intel to the Viceroy.
Yes,my Lord.
What a...
Is that Cornelia?
Relics of a forgotten age.
Darlton,in here? Correct?
Yes,my Lady. Shall we accompany you?
Not for this level of resistance.
Understood.
Surrender at once,you feeble-minded Elevens!
Down with Britannia!
Doesn't seem Zero is here.
No point in going after them one at a time,I suppose.
Vermin. Rot like the filth that you are!
Hi,Lelouch! I returned home.
Hi,there! Welcome back,Miss Sayoko.
I've got a special present for you today.
Really? What could it be?
H'm.
Ah... Ah!
This hand...
Thank heaven.
I knew it. I just knew you'd be alright.
It's been a long time,Nunnaly.
So,tell me you will stay the night,won't you?
Suzaku's enrolled as a student at Ashford Academy now.
So you can see him anytime you want to.
Is that true?
Well,I still have military duties,so I can't be here every day.
Oh,you're... you're still in the military?
Don't worry.
I've been reassigned to the Engineering Corps.
It's a lot less dangerous.
How cool. Engineering,huh.
Oh,let me help you.
You just sit down.
Unlike seven years ago we get to be your hosts now.
Uh... huh.
It's funny. You're lot more mellow than you used to be.
And you are a bit more rough.
Ha-ha. I suppose.
Huh? I told you to stay in my room.
That boy out there,he is the Britanian soldier from Shinjuku,isn't he?
Is that wise?
Don't worry,it's fine. He's...
Huh?
He is a friend... from the past.
You getting out,Jeremiah.
Lord Guilford! You see I'm innocent,don't you?
Well,it seems in the eyes of the court you are anyway,Orange Boy.
Huh?
Whatever the truth is,Zero got away.
And you Pure Bloods let it happen.
You've been demoted three ranks for failure.
You have two options to choose from.
Starting over as a pilot,or cultivating in orange farm.
You should come by again. Nunnaly would enjoy it.
Sure. But...
Huh?
Lelouch,I... I don't think we should be seen together at school.
What do you mean?
Think,how would you explain it.
Being friends with an Honorary Britanian?
You have to guard your secret.
No one can know your royalty.
Ah.
And the same goes for Nunnaly.
I don't wanna cause you any trouble.
Doing it again,huh? Everyone's needs but your own.
Again?
Forget it.
Eh,thanks for having me. It was a lot of fun.
I'll uh,see you later.
Right.
I'm so glad,you know?
Huh?
I never thought we'd get another chance to talk like this.
Why did they do it?
So,what's the deal? Something happen to ya yesterday or what?
You didn't even show up for the council meeting.
You know,I kinda tanked that history exam.
Please,I don't buy that. The way you study? Uh...
Stop you guys...
It hasn't made news yet,but the Blood of the Samurai faction was wiped out by Cornelia.
They were the largest group we had in central Japan.
Look,Zero. It won't be long until she comes after us.
Just keep your head. Our chance will come.
But...
Sit tight. I'll contact you later.
Humph.
It's getting too overly familiar. Maybe I better cut my ties with them.
Nina!
Ah! I'm sorry. Am I too loud?
Not at all. Why are you here? What about class?
Oh...
Something wrong?
Well,it's... I dunno,a little scary
Scary?
We have a transfer student in our class now.
It's that boy who was accused of murdering Prince Clovis.
He is an Eleven.
Oh...
Thanks for all the repeat business.
Although the name on the account we debit has a guy's name on it,is that okay?
Huh? Trying to hide your mask,huh?
Unlike my geass,the mask is a physical piece of evidence.
Huh?
All right,Lelouch? The tea is ready when you are.
That smell! Hey,did you order pizza again?
I'm racking up reward points.
I'll be right down,okay?
Lelouch.
Maybe you should cut down on the pizza. You don't want a blubbery belly.
Just don't touch or rub it,okay?
Ooh,scary!
Hm? What the heck?
Hm. Yeah,I was wondering if that was going on.
They're just being cruel to Suzaku.
No. It's just... Hm.
These things take time. People will come around.
Isn't there anything you can do,though?
I mean he is your friend.
Hey,give that back!
Ah... Lelouch?
Yeah,a cat. Ah,stupid little cat!
You've gotta be kidding me.
There's no way I'm getting exposed by a lousy feline!
Huh? That wasn't my fault,was it?
I didn't touch or rub anything.
{\fnLeviBrush\fs60\b1}CODE GEASS\NLelouch of the Rebellion
Yeah,that's right.
I think a cat ran off with something pretty important to him.
Important?
I'm not sure what exactly,but I'm positive it was something of value to him.
Because... I've never heard my brother sound like that.
He was completely hysterical.
That's weird. What could be so important to the guy?
A love letter?
An embarrassing photo?
Poetry he wrote?
Poetry...
Hee-hee-hee.
Leave it to us!
We'll get our hands on the thing before Lelouch has a chance to blink.
Just you wait.
If I had those terrorists with me,we could encircle the enemy.
Maybe Kallen?
No,she is suspicious of me as it is.
Waah!
Ughh...get it together!
So,anyway I told him to buzz off,you know.
Totally? And then?
Come on. You can guess,can't you?
Uh? What's up with that cat?
Is that the mask Zero wears?
Or am I crazy?
No way. Why would it be here?
You two saw it?
Forget everything you've just seen!
Sure. No problem at all.
Good.
This is Milly Ashford,your Student Council President.
CAT HUNT,everybody!
Cat hunt?
There is a cat loose on campus that needs to be rounded up.
Put everything on hold,people.
Put everything on hold,people.
And whoever catches our feline friend,will get an Extra Special Prize,
a big ol' kiss from one of the members of the Student Council.
Ah-hahaha...
Members of... Wait! Like,me?
Exactly!
You've been hanging around the Student Council,haven't ya?
Wouldn't mind a taste of those lips.
It's not gonna be like some lame peck on the cheek though,is it?
A kiss on the cheek would be fine with me.
Wait. We can choose where she plants it?
Yeah. All right!
There's no way that's how I'm gonna get my first kiss!
What? From a member of the Student Council?
Does that include Lelouch?
Actually I would prefer Milly.
Ah. Could you get back in the closet,please?
Hut hut,fight!
We have the advantage of mobility.
Hurry,you look for catnips!
will prevail!
And when you do catch that cat,bring what it's carrying to me,to me,to me!
Milly? Stay out of this,will ya?
Offering people up as prizes,that's why I hate Britanians.
I could hardly believe it.
I was like,floored when I heard it. Ha ha.
Damn it! Why do I have to pretend like I'm sick and feeble?
Oh,yaah! Huh. Jeez,I'm sorry about that... ah,Shirley!
Why are you dressed like that?
I didn't have time to change.
They're gonna make us kiss somebody.
We've gotta hurry!
I'm with you.
Nunnaly,is there anything about this cat that's special?
Hmm...
I think that its leg must be hurt,because its footsteps sounded off to me.
And,uh...
Oh,I almost forgot. It meowed like this.
Miaow!
Meeow!
The school seems so laidback,in spite of the fact that they're in mourning.
You suppose Suzaku will be alright in here?
Never mind that. The university here...
Don't worry. I've made arrangements with them.
Hmm. They still didn't have to kick poor Lancelot out,though.
I know. Even if they did say Elevens aren't acceptable.
Okay! Let's go!
What happens if a member of the Student Council catches the cat?
We don't get a prize,do we?
Do we get a kiss? But of course.
Is that so.
Well,what are we waiting around for,then. This is my day to shine!
Hey,no speeding on campus!
O.K. We do this right and our lips will be safe.
Shirley,you cover the rear. Humph.
Oh,wait a sec!
What's the matter?
Who would you wanna get a kiss from?
Is there anyone in particular?
Huh?
It wouldn't be Lelou,would it?
Uh. Just what would make you think that?
Oh,how... I guess it... it's just...
Hey,that's...
Suzaku!
Lelouch! You're looking for the cat,too?
Up there.
Suzaku,wait!
Don't go up there!
But the Student Council President said to catch it.
Don't worry about it. I'll get the cat.
I was always more agile than you.
Remember when that little bird got loose?
Quit talking ancient history.
It was only 7 years ago.
Oh,for Pete's sake...
He always was an exercise nut
So,someone's got it cornered,huh?
Who's the lucky winner?
Up there!
Suzaku?
Easy now. You don't have to be scared.
Suzaku,come back!
It's alright. Leave this to me.
That's funny. He never went along with the crowd like this.
Waaah!
Oh!
Huh? Ah... Lelouch!
Are you... okay?
Y... Yeah.
Is it possible? Those two are...
Pretty calm for someone on the verge of death.
Yeah,right. I was just limp with fear.
Huuuh.
Hey,what's going on?
That transfer student just saved Lelouch from a really closed call.
Ah... hah.
I think it's the same cat from the other day.
You saved him. Thank you so much,Suzaku.
Yeah. Way to go there,new guy.
That cat was carrying something,wasn't it?
Yeah,there was something on its head.
But I never really got a good look at it.
Guess it's slipped off when I wasn't looking.
So,where is Lelou?
Eh,He said he forgot something. Told me to go ahead.
That's it! The embarrassing secret that he's hiding.
So,that's it,Madam President?
Hm?
Aaah,after all this time I thought I had some dirt on you.
Yeah. He almost lost his cool for once.
So,ah... do you two know each other,then?
Yeah,but... He is an Eleven.
No. I just...
He is my friend.
Madam President,would you permit him as a member of the Student Council?
Huh?
The rules are clear. All student are required to join a club.
Although...
Uh...
Well,you are the Vice President.
I suppose I can't refuse.
Well then,I'd say that's the end of that.
Now,come here you two. Lend me an ear.
Now,come here you two. Lend me an ear.
There you go,the reward Miss Milly promised.
Since you both caught the cat,you'll just have to settle for me,almost a student council member.
Alright then,let's celebrate the catching of the cat!
Everything's on the new guy,naturally.
Oh,back off!
Hi,there! I'm Shirley. Pleasure to meet ya.
Oh,right. I'm Rivalz.
Milly Ashford,Student Council President.
The pleasure is mine.
And now,His royal Majesty,the 98th Emperor of the Holy Britannian Empire.
All men,are not created equal.
Some are born swifter of foot,
some with greater beauty,
some are born into poverty,
and others born sick and feeble.
Both in birthland and upbringing,
in sheer scope of ability every human is inherently different.
Yes,that is why people discriminate against one another,
which is why there is struggle,competition,and the unfaltering march of progress.
Inequality,is not wrong,equality is.
What of the EU,which made equality a right,rabble politics by a popularity contest.
The Chinese Federation,with its equal distribution of wealth,a nation of lazy dullards.
But not our beloved Britannia,we fight,we compete,evolution is continuous.
Evolution,such a pretty little word.
Britannia alone moves forward,advancing steadily into the future.
Even the death of my son Clovis demonstrates Britannia's unswerving commitment to progress.
We will fight hard.
We shall struggle,compete,plunder,and dominate.
And in the end,the future shall be ours.
All Hail Britannia!
All Hail Britannia! All Hail Britannia! ...
So,this is Lelouch's enemy. Well...
All hail Britannia! All hail Britannia!
{\fade(255,0,255,0,500,5500,8000)}Subtitle: Willing
Yukedomo kemonomichi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Walking along the animal path
Shishi yotorayoto hoe\N{\c&H00FF00&}Roaring with the lions and tigers
Akane sasu sora no kanata ni mahoroba\N{\c&H00FF00&}Paradise lying far across a sky dyed red
Yuushuu no kodoku ni samayou seishun wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To a youth wandering,imprisoned in loneliness
Yowasato ikari ga sugata naki teki desu ka\N{\c&H00FF00&}Are weakness and hatred shapeless enemies?
Chichi yo madaware wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}Oh father,I am still...
Onore wo shirigatashi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Learning who I am
Sakidatsu anira no\N{\c&H00FF00&}As I pursue the backs I no longer see
Mienai senakawo oeba\N{\c&H00FF00&}Of the elder brothers who have gone before me
Mayoi no hitoyo ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}In the night I spend lost
Myoujou wa izanau\N{\c&H00FF00&}The morning star beckons to me
Shi shite owaranu\N{\c&H00FF00&}This will not end in my death
Yume wo kogaredomo\N{\c&H00FF00&}I long for my dream
Tashika na kimi kosowaga inochi\N{\c&H00FF00&}My faith in you sustains my life
Reppu no kouya de\N{\c&H00FF00&}In the windswept wilderness
Chou yo hanayoto iki\N{\c&H00FF00&}Living with the butterflies and flowers
Tokoshie no haru ni sakisou maboroshi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Blooming together in a mirage of eternal Spring
Kondaku nojunketsu\N{\c&H00FF00&}If my purity seems muddied
Kono mi wayogoretemo\N{\c&H00FF00&}And my body seems filthy
Kokoro no nishiki wo shinjiteite kudasai\N{\c&H00FF00&}Please believe in the finery within my heart
Hahayo kesshite ware wa namidawo misene domo\N{\c&H00FF00&}Oh mother,I will show no tears
Ashimoto no\N{\c&H00FF00&}They vanish like...
Kusa ni tsuyu wa kiemosede\N{\c&H00FF00&}The dew in the grass beneath my feet
The word "repudiate" is half-hearted.
If my father is the symbol of Britannia,\Nthen he must be crushed utterly!
And if my sister Cornelia stands in my path,\Nshe will suffer the same fate!
Even though you don't\Nknow it yet,I have power.
As long as I possess the Geass,\NI can do this by myself!
{\fs75\pos(960,650)}ATTACK CORNELIA

