The date was August 10 in the year 2010 of the Imperial Calendar.
The Holy Britannian Empire had just declared war upon Japan.
Confronted by Britannia's newest weapon,the formidable Knightmare Frame,
Japan fell to its enemy in less than a month.
The conquered nation was stripped of its freedom,rights,culture and dignity.
Finally,even its name was taken away.
11.
The name of Japan and its people was replaced with a mere number.
{\fade(255,0,255,0,500,5500,8000)}Subtitle: Willing
Jibun wo sekai sae mo\N{\c&H00FF00&}The moment when I might be able...
Kaete shimae sou na shunkan wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To change myself and even the world
Itsumo sugu soba ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}It's always right there at my side
Kakusenu iradachi to\N{\c&H00FF00&}Even as I stood still,looking at myself
Tachitsukusu jibun wo mitsume\N{\c&H00FF00&}With undisguised frustration
Mayoi nagara nayami nagara\N{\c&H00FF00&}Feeling lost,feeling anguished
Kuyami nagara kimereba ii sa\N{\c&H00FF00&}Feeling mournful,deciding what to do
Kimi ga kureta kotoba hitotsu\N{\c&H00FF00&}All it took was a single word from you
Tomadoi wa kiesari\N{\c&H00FF00&}And my uncertainty vanished
Karappo datta boku no heya ni hikari ga sashita\N{\c&H00FF00&}You let the light shine into what was my empty room
Miageta oozora ga\N{\c&H00FF00&}The sky I had been looking up at...
Aoku sumikitte yuku\N{\c&H00FF00&}Cleared and turned blue
Tozashita madowo hiraku\N{\c&H00FF00&}And I decided to throw open...
Koto kimeta\N{\c&H00FF00&}The windows that were kept closed
Jibun wo sekai sae mo\N{\c&H00FF00&}The moment when I might be able...
Kaete shimae sou na shunkan wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To change myself and even the world
Kanjiru ima koko ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}I feel it right here with me
{\pos(960,900)\fs60\kf100\2a&HFF&}The White Knight Awakens
I don't understand what it is you wanted me to do.
Why did you give me this bizarre power?
How could all these Royal Guards be dead?
What happened here,boy? And why is a Britannian student in a place like this?!
Are you deaf? Answer me or I'll-
Answer me!
I order you to come out. At once!
Who the hell do you think you are to order me?
I see. It only works with direct eye contact.
My name is Allen Spacer,my father's a duke.
Nobility?
My ID card's in my breast pocket.
After you confirm who I am,I'll request your protection.
Keep your hands up in the air,I'll take out your ID.
Now then,hand your Knightmare over to me.
Understood. The code number is XG21G2D4.
Got it.
What the--
So are we having a bad day?
Looks like you missed a chance to go to heaven,Private Kururugi.
I did? Where?
Hmm? Ah,we're still in the Shinjuku Ghetto.
With Prince Clovis nearby this is probably the safest place anywhere.
This is what saved your life,Mr. Suzaku.
You're lucky it was under your protective suit because that's what deflected the bullet.
Is it a keepsake?
Yeah,very.
You Elevens believe that gods live inside of everything,even objects,don't you? I guess this one--
Is Lelou-
What's the latest on the situation?
It looks like the poison gas was released.
Massive Eleven casualties have been reported.
They haven't caught the perpetrators yet.
They haven't,huh? Not yet?
Private Kururugi,how much experience do you have in piloting a Knightmare frame?
But there's no way an Eleven would be made a knight.
Well,supposing you could?
Congratulations,the only Knightmare of its kind awaits you!
Once you take the controls of this big beauty everything will change,you and your world.
Whether you want it to or not.
Those damn Britannians!
Kallen,can the Glasgow still move?
Don't worry Ogi,it's all right. I'll decoy them!
Get the people out of here.
The only ones that'll be captured are those of us in the resistance.
I know but we're trapped,they've got us completely surrounded.
That's because you don't have enough leg strength,right?
You're wrong. You sink when you get fat.
Because you snack,right?
I'll be fine,I burn up twice as many calories.
Ah,Lelou? What in the world have you been doing? Where are you now?
If you keep cutting class,you'll get held back.
Are you near a TV?
A TV?
Sorry,but this is important.
Hang on. Hey,can I change the channel?
Huh? To what?
The news,is there anything about Shinjuku?
News? Uhh,let's see...
There's nothing on. Traffic restrictions?
Why is it restricted?
I don't know. They're not saying.
I get it. Once they finish everything off,they'll release news that favors the military.
Ooh,you're gambling again,aren't you?
I've warned you before more than once how dangerous that is!
Yep,you caught me.
By the way,tell my little sister that I'm gonna be late home tonight,would you? Thanks.
Oooh! Why does he always hang up on me like that?!
The number you have called is beyond service range.
Oh darn it,not this again.
They need to keep a lid on this information,
so it'll be hard for them to call in reinforcements.
They'll have to make do with the pieces they have on the board.
But I'm hemmed in here,and it'll be tough to break through by myself.
Gaining refuge carries its own risk,too.
I want payback for being dragged into your fight.
It's our Glasgow friend.
Just 30 minutes left!
The west entrance.
Use the tracks to move to the west entrance.
Who's this! How do you know this code?!
That doesn't matter.
If you wanna win,you're just gonna have to trust me.
To win?
Okay,what am I supposed to do now?
You pathetic Eleven.
If you simply run away,this hunt hasn't much to offer in the way of sport.
Since you trusted me,you're gonna win.
Jump onto the train!
Gotcha!
You think you can get through that way,hmm?
If that's your plan,then...
You! Go after the Glasgow.
Yes,My Lord!
What the...?
Shot by friendly fire?
What's your name and your unit?!
We're after the one armed Glasgow.
Oh my god! A terrorist?!
You son of a--! Aaaaah!
You saved me.But how did you get ahold of a Sutherland?
What? Where did he go?
Kallen! What the hell was that radio message earlier?
What? He contacted you,too?
Sure did. And Yoshida's group ought to be here soon.
Are you in charge?
Ah,yeah.
I present to you the cargo in that train over there.
They're tools for your victory.
If you want to use them to win,then follow my orders.
There's more in here!
Here,too!
Amazing! Maybe we should give this guy a chance.
All this? But how?
Woman in the Glasgow!
Y-yes!
Stay where you are. Your unit's gonna run decoy. You got that?
Understood.
Energy filler status?
About 15 minutes worth.
Then recharge it!
In 10 minutes,I'll contact you with your next instructions.
This is wearing me out.
Regardless,I'll need determination to succeed.
After all,I'm betting my life in this game.
The terrorists are mixed among the Eleven populous
and they're mounting a minor resistance against us.
But they pose little threat to our vastly superior army.
We know that. Moving on.
Understood,Your Highness. The gas capsules will be--
What the public thinks.
Yes. We’ll keep searching for her.
Either way I want her captured dead or alive.
Hey,are you certain about this whole thing?
They've all had their IFFs removed. What if this is a trap?
The other side has total advantage in this war.
They don't need to set any traps.
All right people,let's move. Get to your assigned points.
P1,can you move?
It operates basically the same as what you're used to.
Can’t you tell us who you are,at least your name?
I can’t do that. What if these signals are being intercepted?
Anyway,if Q1 is on schedule,enemy Sutherlands,probably two of them,will reach you in 23 seconds.
Shoot them through the wall.
Aaarrrg,he's out of his mind.
Everyone,double check your weapons.
What?! Are you serious?
Enemy spotted at point F 31.
A feint,eh? How pedestrian.
Tell Laslo’s squad to go straight in.
Have Eugen and Valerie strike from the rear.
3,2,1,fire!
Wh-What?!
Sir Eugen and Sir Valerie,both lost.
Hmm? An ambush?
An ID signal can be a double edged sword.
Besides,if the terrorists follow the orders I issue,
my task at hand is sure to be completed.
P1,P4,P7,move a hundred meter to the right and fire your slash harkens toward 3 o’clock.
You heard him. Do what the voice says.
Damn,what else does he want us to do?
P5,ready?
Yeah. Quit calling me that.
Ah! They're using the same--
The enemy's moving towards G 28.
Send Laslo's Squad,I mean Glaubey's Squad!
This means terrorists have our military weaponry?
Sir Glaubey has ejected! His unit's been lost!
Change our codes,they're intercepting our transmission.
We already have sir,four times!
Do it again.
This failure is unacceptable.
...Forgive me.
Good afternoon.
What is it? We’re in the middle of an operation.
I’d say it's time to deploy the ASEEC's special weapon.
We've no time for this right now.
R2,fire anchor
B7,use UN ordnance.
N group,you'll continue your advance.
You bloody Eleven!
We just lost Laslo's Squad.
So do it. We’ll have to bring up Quincey’s squad.
My Lord,that will break the encirclement.
Now then,the enemy has five options. Their move.
Reinforce the breach with some of the units guarding me.
All we know for certain is that enemy forces are here.
Who ordered them to break formation?
Well that’s a more stupid move than I expected.
You,Q1,do you have an area map?
Yes,I have a map of the old town.
But it has no current land marks.
It’ll do.
All right,send in Burts and the others too.
Mission number 3 now.
Concentrate our forces there. Surround them.
Is everything prepared?
The enemy’s main force is that center dot.
Finish every one of them off.
What?! Where's the enemy?
With this,I call check.
HAHAHAHAHA! My plan worked,didn’t it.
I can do it. I can.
I can defeat Britannia!
Who? Who in the hell am I up against?
What if he’s even better than Todo?
Lloyd!
Yes,Your Highness.
Can it win,will your toy beat them?
My Lord,please be so kind as to call it Lancelot.
{\fnLeviBrush\fs60\b1}CODE GEASS\NLelouch of the Rebellion
Z-01 Lancelot now activating.
Lancelot activating.
Releasing hatch.
Z-01 Lancelot standby for activation.
Pallet extension initiating.
Did you read the manual?
Pretty much.
Well done.
You scored at the top of the class in the simulator.
Hey,look.
About what you told me earlier.
Huh? Ah,it could be.
But the possibility is nearly zero.
But that means there's still a chance,right?
Yes,I'm afraid that's true.
Even so,you're not to do anything reckless.
The new system is not outfitted with an ejection mechanism.
OK. I understand,Miss Cecile.
That's it?
Yes,the advanced weapon developed by us in the Advanced Special Envoy Engineering Corps,
Lancelot,
the world's first seventh generation Knightmare Frame.
Well,if you're ready,Suzaku,shall we proceed with the initial startup?
Initial startup. Now percieving from phase twenty.
Equiping energy filler.
Confirm pre-start. Energy filler now at full output.
30 seconds to reach critical voltage.
Core Luminance,shifting phase.
Initiating devicer setup.
Confirming entry of devicer into Z-01.
Individual ID registration confirmed.
Confirm man-machine interface. Engage.
Yggdrasil Resonance comfirmed. Rejection Responce,weak.
Devicer's Stress Respond.
All readings,nominal...
So far,it's going per the data.
...status,all green. Status of back up tactical bank,authorized.
Secondary confirmation,given.
Lancelot,activate ME-boost.
Lancelot,launch!
HAHAHAHA! Running full throttle right out of the gate.
Cooler than the manual. With this...!
Huh? What is that?
It doesn't look like a Sutherland.
Hahaha... Another push and the check point will fall.
This is B group,reporting enemy presence.
Hm? Reinforcements? Real battle is different,isn’t it?
Status?
Every one ejected,but they took out four units in nothing flat.
Enemy numbers?
Just one.
I think it’s a new model. I’ve never seen anything like it- Ah!
What’s happening out there?
Bastard!
What? It reflects bullets?
Arrh,what do we do? Ishida! Ah!
Useless so called terrorists.
With all the resources they have,they're being beaten by one unit.
Damn it!
Yes,I can do this. With Lancelot I can stop all this at once.
N4,N5,hold there.
When the rear units arrive,surround that thing.
Gotcha.
We can't stop it!
N units,what is it?
What happened? Something I didn't foresee?
For heaven’s sake.
Now I’ll owe my older brother a debt I don’t need to incur.
It's for the best,though.
Ah!
P1! Report!
The enermy,can it really be only one unit?
These readings are even higher than predicted.
It's because our pilot is taking his job very seriously.
If I can stop all the Knightmares,then this battle is over.
No matter what it takes,I've gotta save Lelouch and that girl.
You mean this thing's what's ruining my plan?
Are you the guy that's in command?
Nothing more than a pilot. How dare he!
No choice,I've gotta get out of here.
Hey,I’m returning the favor.
I can't--
I must remember that the most vital element in battle is the human one.
That damn monster's unstoppable!
Bastard. He's tearing things up for no reason!
Eeeeeeeeek!
In the midst of battle he rescues someone?
Hm,I concede you the tactical victory here. Nevertheless...
Huh? He saved someone?
Yes,so it would seem.
Hm... It's very strange of him.
Suzaku,are you tired?
We'll call it quits for today.
No. I'm fine. Please let me keep going.
Be careful with his operational time!
Yes,sir.
My,that boy's an excellent piece of equipment.
Stop there,your ID.
This is Prince Clovis’s personal transport.
At last,the check point.
And barely guarded,per my plan.
Your plan?
That’s right. Now I'd like you to let me pass.
Yes,sir. Understood.
Kallen!
It's your fault. This is what happened when you oppose the Britannians.
What!? Why you gutless coward?
How many people were killed because of this!?
Shut up! Do you know how many of us were killed or captured? Do ya?
Quit crying.
Ougi,who was that voice we heard?
Damned if I know. He doesn't answer when I call so maybe he b--
There,you see!
Instead of following somebody we don't even know,we should've use the poison gas.
But he--
Damn Nagata to hell!
So this is where you Eleven vermin scurried off to.
Prepared to fire!
Naoto!
Commence--
Attention all forces.
Cease fire at once.
Cease fire?
I Clovis,third prince of Britannia and royal viceroy of Area Eleven,here by command you,
all forces are ordered to cease fire at once.
You also cease destruction of any buildings or property.
All casualties,whether Britannian or Eleven,shall be treated equally and without prejudice.
In the name of Clovis la Britannia,you are here by ordered,cease fire at once.
I shall allow no further fighting.
Are you satisfied?
Very. Well done.
And what shall we do now?
Sing a few lively ballads,or perhaps a nice game of chess?
That has a familiar ring.
Hmm?
Don’t you recall?
The two of us used to play chess together as boys.
Of course,I would always win.
What?
Remember? At the Aries Villa?
You,who are you?
It’s been a long time,big brother.
The eldest son of the late consort Marianne and seventeenth in line to the imperial throne,
Lelouch vi Britannia,at your service.
Lelouch?! B-But I thought--
That I was dead? You were wrong.
I have returned,Your Highness.
And I’ve come back to change everything.
{\fade(255,0,255,0,500,5500,8000)}Subtitle: Willing
Yukedomo kemonomichi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Walking along the animal path
Shishi yotorayoto hoe\N{\c&H00FF00&}Roaring with the lions and tigers
Akane sasu sora no kanata ni mahoroba\N{\c&H00FF00&}Paradise lying far across a sky dyed red
Yuushuu no kodoku ni samayou seishun wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To a youth wandering,imprisoned in loneliness
Yowasato ikari ga sugata naki teki desu ka\N{\c&H00FF00&}Are weakness and hatred shapeless enemies?
Chichi yo madaware wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}Oh father,I am still...
Onore wo shirigatashi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Learning who I am
Sakidatsu anira no\N{\c&H00FF00&}As I pursue the backs I no longer see
Mienai senakawo oeba\N{\c&H00FF00&}Of the elder brothers who have gone before me
Mayoi no hitoyo ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}In the night I spend lost
Myoujou wa izanau\N{\c&H00FF00&}The morning star beckons to me
Shi shite owaranu\N{\c&H00FF00&}This will not end in my death
Yume wo kogaredomo\N{\c&H00FF00&}I long for my dream
Tashika na kimi kosowaga inochi\N{\c&H00FF00&}My faith in you sustains my life
Reppu no kouya de\N{\c&H00FF00&}In the windswept wilderness
Chou yo hanayoto iki\N{\c&H00FF00&}Living with the butterflies and flowers
Tokoshie no haru ni sakisou maboroshi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Blooming together in a mirage of eternal Spring
Kondaku nojunketsu\N{\c&H00FF00&}If my purity seems muddied
Kono mi wayogoretemo\N{\c&H00FF00&}And my body seems filthy
Kokoro no nishiki wo shinjiteite kudasai\N{\c&H00FF00&}Please believe in the finery within my heart
Hahayo kesshite ware wa namidawo misene domo\N{\c&H00FF00&}Oh mother,I will show no tears
Ashimoto no\N{\c&H00FF00&}They vanish like...
Kusa ni tsuyu wa kiemosede\N{\c&H00FF00&}The dew in the grass beneath my feet
I thought it was impossible.
How can a lone student change the world?
It isn't realistic.
Just think about it a\Nmoment and you see that.
Still...
Now that I've been given the opportunity...
There may be a move I have to play.
{\fs75\pos(960,650)}THE FALSE CLASSMATE

