Open fire!
Gloucester?
It's supposed to be in Serupham.
Shoddy oversized imitation Knightmares.
They would've been wise to surrender from the start.
What?
So Cornelia. A single unit did this?
Another victory. Area 18 has been established.
: My Lady,about our next course of action.
Sorry to have you clean up after my foolish younger brother.
Please don't apologize,my Lady. We live to serve and our place is with you.
Humph. Do you think the Area 11 needs our usual treatment?
Yes,my Lady.
Good.
I'll drive you into the open,Zero.
Clovis will be avenged.
{\fade(255,0,255,0,500,5500,8000)}Subtitle: Willing
Jibun wo sekai sae mo\N{\c&H00FF00&}The moment when I might be able...
Kaete shimae sou na shunkan wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To change myself and even the world
Itsumo sugu soba ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}It's always right there at my side
Kakusenu iradachi to\N{\c&H00FF00&}Even as I stood still,looking at myself
Tachitsukusu jibun wo mitsume\N{\c&H00FF00&}With undisguised frustration
Mayoi nagara nayami nagara\N{\c&H00FF00&}Feeling lost,feeling anguished
Kuyami nagara kimereba ii sa\N{\c&H00FF00&}Feeling mournful,deciding what to do
Kimi ga kureta kotoba hitotsu\N{\c&H00FF00&}All it took was a single word from you
Tomadoi wa kiesari\N{\c&H00FF00&}And my uncertainty vanished
Karappo datta boku no heya ni hikari ga sashita\N{\c&H00FF00&}You let the light shine into what was my empty room
Miageta oozora ga\N{\c&H00FF00&}The sky I had been looking up at...
Aoku sumikitte yuku\N{\c&H00FF00&}Cleared and turned blue
Tozashita madowo hiraku\N{\c&H00FF00&}And I decided to throw open...
Koto kimeta\N{\c&H00FF00&}The windows that were kept closed
Jibun wo sekai sae mo\N{\c&H00FF00&}The moment when I might be able...
Kaete shimae sou na shunkan wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To change myself and even the world
Kanjiru ima koko ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}I feel it right here with me
{\pos(960,900)\fs60\kf80\2a&HFF&}The Princess and The Witch
I'm back.
Welcome home,Lelouch.
I'm so glad. I was worried.
I'm assuming you ate out tonight judging from your appearance.
Thank goodness. I thought maybe you've gotten caught up in all the uproar caused by that man Zero.
I tried calling you but you didn't answer your cellphone.
I wanted to tell you Ms. C.C.'s been waiting as well.
C.C.?
Your friend goes by such an unusual name,only her initials.
Yeah.
I was just wondering,is C.C. your girlfriend?
Huh?
He made a promise about our future together. Right?
A future together? You mean marriage?
No! No,that isn't what she was talking about.
It's like a... she's kidding around.
No,I'm not.
Well you're certainly doing this sooner than most.
But everyone's different,aren't they? So I suppose it isn't that strange.
And if you feel like you're ready for... Oh.
Oh,C.C. Look what you've done,you're soaking wet.
Come on,let's get you to the bathroom and into a dry change of clothes.
Nunnaly,stay here and I'll clean it up in a minute.
And she was kidding before. Kidding. Just a dumb joke. That's all.
Who are you?
She said my name. I'm C.C.
That's not I meant. Why aren't you...
...supposed to be dead?
So,do you like the power that I gave you?
As I thought,it was you.
Dissatisfied?
On the contrary,I'm grateful.
It allows me speed up my schedule tremendously,which is a huge help.
Your schedule?
Yes. My schedule for obliterating Britania.
I would've had to wait much longer before I could've made the initial move.
You believe you can destroy it simply by using that power?
I intended to do it without this power.
I just knew that he'd turn out to be a fascinating guy.
But what'll you do now? I'm sure the military is after you.
Not the entire military,only a small faction of it.
So it shouldn't be difficult to find hiding place.
I can make do here.
What? You expect to stay here?
A gentleman would sleep on the floor.
Don't joke around.
My being caught would cause trouble for you too.
It's dangerous to stay together.
If I wander the streets,they'll find me.
This isn't about you. It's my situation.
I hate stubbornness.
You sure take things casually,don't you?
How did you manage to survive before this? What did you do before now?
And what's the deal with that so-called contract you spoke of...
Good night,Lelouch.
Fukushima,Kouchi,Hiroshima.
This has been the seventh occurence since that man named Zero raised his head.
:It seems the other groups are following his lead and putting up a valiant fight.
And now,suspicions about that "Orange" thing have cost Margrave Jeremiah his command.
Maybe he wasn't good enough.
Thanks to him,connections between the police and the administration are screwed up.
It's made a fine mess for us as well.
Help them Tohdoh!
Zero has thrown the Britannians into chaos.
Now is the time for us in the Japan Liberation Front to make our stand!
Calm down.
The information of Kyoto giving the Guren Mk-II to Zero hasn't been confirmed.
If we pay too much attention to Zero we may trip ourselves up.
So,what did "Orange" turn out to be anyway?
Well?
You know for someone who isn't willing to answer any questions,you certainly do ask a lot of them.
If you don't want to answer my questions,you don't have to. Just as I don't.
Humph. There is no "Orange". It's something I made up. But...
The more they claim to be comrades of like-mind,
the easier it is to divide them with the thorns of suspicion.
H'm.
Everyone on earth is looking for you.
Because of you the world is going through an upheaval.
So,is this it? Is this what you wanted to see?
No. This uproar's simply a means to an end.
The world is destined to descended into a greater chaos.
Case No.107 Private Suzaku Kururugi,Area 11 Military Forces.
In the murder of His Highness Prince Clovis you are no longer a suspect,
and are hereby set free due to lack of evidence.
What happened? I'm free.
Out of the way,please.
Look out below!
Oh!
Uh,are you all right?
I'm sorry. I wasn't aware you were down here until I had leapt.
Well,don't worry.
I wasn't expecting a girl to come falling out of the sky and into my arms,either.
Oh,my...
Huh? Is there something wrong?
Yes! There is something wrong.
Huh?
The truth is bad guys are chasing me.
So considering the circumstances could you help me,please?
We must get rid of this "Orange" character before Princess Cornelia assumes her new post.
Now the loyalty of us Pure Bloods is being called into question.
Are the reports we've been hearing true? Lord Jeremiah was bribed?
Do you know what this "Orange" means?
In any case,Lord Jeremiah is definitely hiding something.
Saying he can't recall anything,Bartley offered the same excuse.
Lord Jeremiah's memory is muddled.
Exactly like those of the men in Shinjuku whose Sutherlands were stolen.
And...
We haven't introduced ourselves yet,have we? My name is...
Euphie.
Euphie?
Yes.
My name's ...
Don't tell me.
Huh?
'Cause I already know it.
You're a celebrity,son of Prime Minister Genbu Kururugi,Private Suzaku Kururugi.
Humph. You lied before. There's no one chasing you at all,right?
Meow!
What?
Meow meow. Aww,does the kitty's paw hurt?
Oh,meow meow meow!
Meow? (Sniff-sniff) Meow!
Meow meow.
H'm...huh.
Oh,my...
We're running late. I hope he's still waiting for us.
Considering the charge,did they really release him?
: Yes. They had no evidence.
I'm sure they put him through the third degree because of that Zero incident,uh-huh?
What? Why is he...
Aha.
If you want to enjoy...
Do you have trouble with cats?
H'm. I like them fine. However...
H'm. The attraction isn't mutual.
I think an unrequited love is a mark of a kind person. Oh.
The kitty ran away.
Oo. Euphie.
Why did you tell me that lie when we met?
Do you ask because you're concerned about me?
Huh? Um... of course.
Good! Then you can accompany me some more.
Alright.
Come on. It'll be fun.
You know,being here is just like being in Britania. I feel right at home.
Are you from the homeland?
Uh-huh. I was a student there up until last week.
Last week? So what're you doing now?
By student do you mean high school?
You can go sightsee anytime,can't you?
Heh-heh. You ask a lot of questions.
Ah,sorry.
Oh! No,I don't mean it like that.
You see... today is the last day of my vacation.
I wanted to see as much of Area 11 as I could because I'd like to know what kinda place it is.
Well,you didn't need me for that.
No,I'm glad I could see it with you.
Is that right?
Suzaku,would you mind taking me to one more place,please?
Your wish is my command,my Lady. Where to?
Take me to Shinjuku.
Suzaku Kururugi,please escort me there.
{\fnLeviBrush\fs60\b1}CODE GEASS\NLelouch of the Rebellion
Lelouch?

Do you have a moment?
Sure. What is it?
About that phone call the other day...
Phone call?
Yeah,you know,when you and I were in the bathroom.
Uh-huh.
Can you find out what the caller ID was?
I want to contact that person again.
It was a school phone,so I'm not sure such... EEK!?
I see. Make sense. I should have known.
That girl...
What? Is there something wrong...Woa?
Huh? No way.
Excuse me. What are you doing?
Ah... what indeed.
To think I turn to homeland like this,I wish I never involved the damn girl.
Are you insane? You can't go walking around.
Don't act strict with me,I never leave the school ground so it's fine.
It's not. You can't do as you like here,you don't belong.
I don't belong anywhere.
Hmm? What's with her?
Oh,is she doing again today?
Again?
She is going to be marking the wall like that every day,because I used my Geass on her to make her do it.
Geass?
The name of the power I have. That's what I heard when we first made contact.
You testing how long it lasts?
I need to know the specs of my weapon,don't I?
So behave or I'll try it on you.
Would it work on me?
Oh relax,you and I are in this together,
I won't do anything to endanger us or our unique partnership.
The Shinjuku Ghetto... ruined again.
The residents were starting to return too.
Man,they didn't use RG on the Elevens. I figured they wouldn't.
Hey,look! Those are marks of Hummer rounds. Get a clear shot of it.
Say cheese!
Got it.
Okay,me next.
{\i1}This is true,right? This info about Zero?{\i0}
{\i1}Yes,sir.{\i0}\N{\i1}Lord Kewell contacted me.{\i0}
Right! Set up a cordon around Shinjuku ghetto sector 4!
Cordon Sector 4. Roger.
Okay,ball's in your court now,Lord Kewell.
I wanted to be put through to Lord Jeremiah. But it appears that you're too busy now.
Get out of here,you damn Britanian bastards!
Eh?
Stay here.
How dare a lowly Eleven speak like...
Don't call me Eleven! I'm Japanese.
Wrong. You seem to forget you people lost. You're nothing but a beaten dog!
Grrr... you racist pig.
Stop. Please no violence!
Stay out of this!
You're that...
Are you Suzaku Kururugi?
The guy who killed Clovis?
No,it... it... it was Zero who killed him.
Tchick. This guy is nothing more than a slave.
Big deal. You're an honorary Britanian.
Nobody cares.
You sold your pride,your people,yourself,yet you call yourself Japanese?
No! You're wrong!
I am not wrong!
You stinking Britanian lapdog aaah...
Stop,please!
I've warn you I've been trained for military combat.
Don't make me fight against my own people.
Like hell your own people!
Come on. Just let it go.
Oof,lousy traitor.
Suzaku.
Oh,my... Are you okay?
Yeah,I'm alright.
Well I'm not O.K. Just look at my prime-G and my elex-4.
Why did you wait? Damn it,some honorary citizen you are.
Why'd you let 'em go? You should have killed 'em.
What's a few dead elevens to a guy like you!
Who do you think's taking care of you all these years anyway? Ugh!
I'll not allow you to insult this man any longer you oaf.
To use my Geass,I need to have direct eye contact with the subject.
Transparent objects like eyeglasses present no problem.
The effective range is approximately 270 meters.
And a subject appears to have no memory of events before,during,or after the power is used.
I think this is due to damage caused by the Geass interfering with the brain of the subject.
Also if the signal's optical I can reflect it.
In the short time you had it,you've learned a lot.
My opponent is an Empire that controls more than 1/3 of the entire world.
There's no such thing as being too careful.
I'd understand if you were an Eleven,but you are a Britannian,aren't you?
This opponent may be too large and strong to fight with only Geass for a weapon.
Is it good to be strong?
Is it bad to be weak?
Back then when I was ten,the world seemed like such a terribly sad place.
A world without any hope at all.
Starvation,
disease,
filth,decay,
racism,
constant war and terrorism.
Living in a never-ending cycle of hate.
Rats running in a wheel.
The cycle must be broken. Somebody has to do it.
How idealistic.
Of course,it's doubtful if the one who does it will make all the bad things go away.
I'm not that arrogant,and so...
No one should lose more of the people they love.
At least,a world without war.
And to have this utopia you'd...?
How would you do it?
It's simple.
When somebody wins,the fighting will end.
Somebody?
I don't know how you would do it.
But if I stop trying,then my father's death will have been in vain.
The Prime Minister's death?
My own father died,because he had to sacrifice his life in that war.
Ah.
Jeremiah. You are going to pay for letting Prince Clovis' murderer go free.
Kewell! You dirty coward. That sighting of Zero was a lie,wasn't it?
We have to wipe away our disgrace before Princess Cornelia takes up her post here.
This is how we keep our officials honest.
Suzaku!
Miss Cecile.
It's dangerous here,get in.
The Pure Bloods are having a silly squabble.
Let's get out of here.
Oh,and by the way,what a shame about your acquittal.
Because now you'll have to work for me again.
Wait,please!
Isn't this an opportunity to gather battle data for the Lancelot?
Ah?
Oho?
Suzaku...
I'm sorry,Euphie. We have to say goodbye here.
I need to do this. I think I can stop them with the Lancelot.
I have to try. I... I must!
Damn,it's four against one. Cowards!
Cowards!
Don't worry Jeremiah. We'll say you died in battle.
Your family's name won't be disgraced.
You're serious then?
You actually intend to kill me?
Kewell!
Silence,Orange! We serve the Imperial family.
Why else would we be here?
All hail Britannia!
What,ugh...
Stop it! You're all Britannian soldiers!
That's him,it's that Honorary Britannian.
The advanced weapon,Lancelot.
What business of the Special Corps want here?
Interlopers will die.
No!
I can't stand by and ignore this senseless battle.
Oh my God. They've perfected the MVSes.
Too late,I won't back down.
We're on the same side!
Suzaku Kururugi... is saving me?
We can at least kill Orange.
Lord Jeremiah!
Viletta! Thanks.
Still wanna fight?
Men,stand down.
Kewell!
You... you understand then?
I'm using a chaos mine.
Huh?
No,stop it now!
What?
Ahh!
That Honorary Britannian. He risked his life for...
Everyone,lower your weapons at once.
In my name I command you.
It...can't be.
I am Euphemia li Britannia of the Empire.
And the third princess of the royal family.
Ah! Euphie.
I'm assuming command here. Now fall back.
It is her,it's the princess.
Did you know it was her,Lloyd?
Uh-huh,but she's been a student up until now and hasn't made her public debut yet.
We,we're truly...
We're truly sorry,your Highness!
My Lady!
I had no idea who you were. Please forgive me,Princess.
Suzaku,you and I bear a similar deep pain.
You have lost your father as I have lost my brother.
Ah.
Will you let me help you in your quest...
...to ensure that no one ever again has to suffer the loss of a loved one on the battlefield.
Yes I'm unworthy of your kindness.
I heard what you did,Euphemia. You shouldn't be so reckless.
I know,Sister. Forgive me. But...
You will address me as Viceroy here,Sub-Viceroy Euphemia.
Because we're sisters we need to follow a stricter protocol.
Yes,I understand.
Humph. Now then,give me your report.
Yes,my Lady.
The first order of business is a welcome party we've arranged for your Highness and...
Oh!
Ah.
Sloppy,senile,corrupt.
Where is Zero? I want the enemy of the Empire caught!
Get Zero!
Huh?
I'll be joining the student body here at Ashford Academy beginning today.
My name is Suzaku Kururugi. It's a pleasure to meet you.
{\fade(255,0,255,0,500,5500,8000)}Subtitle: Willing
Yukedomo kemonomichi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Walking along the animal path
Shishi yotorayoto hoe\N{\c&H00FF00&}Roaring with the lions and tigers
Akane sasu sora no kanata ni mahoroba\N{\c&H00FF00&}Paradise lying far across a sky dyed red
Yuushuu no kodoku ni samayou seishun wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To a youth wandering,imprisoned in loneliness
Yowasato ikari ga sugata naki teki desu ka\N{\c&H00FF00&}Are weakness and hatred shapeless enemies?
Chichi yo madaware wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}Oh father,I am still...
Onore wo shirigatashi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Learning who I am
Sakidatsu anira no\N{\c&H00FF00&}As I pursue the backs I no longer see
Mienai senakawo oeba\N{\c&H00FF00&}Of the elder brothers who have gone before me
Mayoi no hitoyo ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}In the night I spend lost
Myoujou wa izanau\N{\c&H00FF00&}The morning star beckons to me
Shi shite owaranu\N{\c&H00FF00&}This will not end in my death
Yume wo kogaredomo\N{\c&H00FF00&}I long for my dream
Tashika na kimi kosowaga inochi\N{\c&H00FF00&}My faith in you sustains my life
Reppu no kouya de\N{\c&H00FF00&}In the windswept wilderness
Chou yo hanayoto iki\N{\c&H00FF00&}Living with the butterflies and flowers
Tokoshie no haru ni sakisou maboroshi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Blooming together in a mirage of eternal Spring
Kondaku nojunketsu\N{\c&H00FF00&}If my purity seems muddied
Kono mi wayogoretemo\N{\c&H00FF00&}And my body seems filthy
Kokoro no nishiki wo shinjiteite kudasai\N{\c&H00FF00&}Please believe in the finery within my heart
Hahayo kesshite ware wa namidawo misene domo\N{\c&H00FF00&}Oh mother,I will show no tears
Ashimoto no\N{\c&H00FF00&}They vanish like...
Kusa ni tsuyu wa kiemosede\N{\c&H00FF00&}The dew in the grass beneath my feet
Yes,I understand. I'm lying.
To Shirley and Rivalz and the others. Even to Suzaku and Nunnaly.
But there's no going back now. I can't turn back.
As long as C.C. and I are bound by our contract,I have to keep at this.
Because I don't wanna lie to myself any more.
{\fs75\pos(960,680)}The Stolen Mask

