Lelouch,a youth of Britannia,had been granted special abilities by a mysterious girl.
Geass,
the power to command others to do absolutely anything.
And Lelouch is determined to use that power to bring the Britannian Empire to its knees.
To avenge his mother,and create a world where his younger sister Nunnally can find happiness.
All the while knowing at the end of his quest,the Britannian Emperor,his father,awaits.
Or at least,that was the hope Lelouch carried in his heart back then...
{\fade(255,0,255,0,500,5500,8000)}Subtitle: Willing
Jibun wo sekai sae mo\N{\c&H00FF00&}The moment when I might be able...
Kaete shimae sou na shunkan wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To change myself and even the world
Itsumo sugu soba ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}It's always right there at my side
Kakusenu iradachi to\N{\c&H00FF00&}Even as I stood still,looking at myself
Tachitsukusu jibun wo mitsume\N{\c&H00FF00&}With undisguised frustration
Mayoi nagara nayami nagara\N{\c&H00FF00&}Feeling lost,feeling anguished
Kuyami nagara kimereba ii sa\N{\c&H00FF00&}Feeling mournful,deciding what to do
Kimi ga kureta kotoba hitotsu\N{\c&H00FF00&}All it took was a single word from you
Tomadoi wa kiesari\N{\c&H00FF00&}And my uncertainty vanished
Karappo datta boku no heya ni hikari ga sashita\N{\c&H00FF00&}You let the light shine into what was my empty room
Miageta oozora ga\N{\c&H00FF00&}The sky I had been looking up at...
Aoku sumikitte yuku\N{\c&H00FF00&}Cleared and turned blue
Tozashita madowo hiraku\N{\c&H00FF00&}And I decided to throw open...
Koto kimeta\N{\c&H00FF00&}The windows that were kept closed
Jibun wo sekai sae mo\N{\c&H00FF00&}The moment when I might be able...
Kaete shimae sou na shunkan wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To change myself and even the world
Kanjiru ima koko ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}I feel it right here with me
{\pos(960,900)\fs60\kf100\2a&HFF&}His Name Is Zero
Do you know anything about this weapon?
Suzaku Kururugi,it was the one used to rob Prince Clovis of his life.
The barrel striations leave no doubt,
and we've done a little homework on you as well.
You're the eldest child of Japan's last acting prime minister,are you not?
Your motive here is clear.
You're making a mistake.
I have never even laid eyes on that gun.
We've found your fingerprints all over this weapon.
You're also suspected of murdering members of the Royal Guard.
Come clean now,and you'll be judged as though you were born a Britannian,
not some worthless Eleven.
You're wrong! I've done nothing!
That was Suzaku they mentioned on the news,wasn't it?
Yep,it looks like he's still alive.
Yeah,it's been ages.
We haven't seen him since the war ended.
Even we...
And Lelouch?
What is it?
It wasn't true what the news said,was it?
Of course not.
Suzaku would never do anything like that. They've just made a mistake.
Yeah... must be.
Right. Well...
Good night,Nunnally.
That's why we should've issued freaking statement sooner.
We could've taken credit for it.
Naoto.
I'm not cut out for this,I'm no leader.
Yes,everything is just as you requested.
We have the best in the business working on it.
Once this slide system is in order,it's all yours.
Once I erased all of the evidence I should forget this ever happen,right?
Truely this is unbitter painful incident for all,
the viceroy of area 11,a beloved prince clovis has been lost to us forever.
However,we can and will bear the weight of this tragedy,
and from this darkest of hours draw strength.
We've lost most crucial parts of the equation.
Can we do it without him?
Don't I wish.
The other units never let go of good pilots.
And even if we got one,they never match his readings.
His operational efficiency clocked at 94 percents. Then you wanna replace him?
You should tell them up,perhaps that let Suzaku go.
He's an honorary Britanian and never loosen.
Ever since general Bartley's disgrace,The purebloods have the military and I am gripped.
The pureblood's what?
Well,from what I understand,they're saying that only pureblood Britanians should be allowed to serve in the military.
Their view is one of their own can never be a criminal.
But if the criminal is an Eleven,
it pays the way for Margrave Jeremiah to shut down the practice of granting natives honorary status.
And what about Suzaku?
He is fake so but decided.
Hey Lelouch!
You've got anything done on later?
After all classes have been cancelled for the day,hawk that I've asking for a rematch.
You are not gambling you guys!
Come on. Don't be such a stick in the mud.
She's right though. Maybe it's time to quit.
Huh?!
I found a better opponent actually.
You did? I don't get it.
You'll cut me in all the action too,right?
A-Hahaha. Better not. It's not really 'of your out ?'.
Britania's resounding victory over Japan...
...opened the unenlightened nation's eyes to it's true place in today's world order.
Since then the empire and area 11 had walked hand in hand down the road to revival.
16 hundred hours at Tokyo tower. Why here of all places?
It was Kururugi who contacted us wasn't it?
Hard to say.
Yeah,but he might have been arrested after his communication with Kallen.
Then we are in danger here. We should go.
Attention please. Paging Miss Kallen Stadtfeld,Ashford Academy.
One of your personal effects has been turned in at the kiosk on the observation deck.
I repeat.
Hi. I'm assuming that this phone is yours,ma'am.
Uhm,something wrong? It is yours isn't it?
Ah,yeah thank you so much.
Oh yeah,there's no debating. Life is better here thanks to Prince Clovis.
I mean it's all due to Britania that we can rebuild as quickly as we did.
Zero?
Uhm... Hello?
I want you to board the outbound train on loop line five. And bring your friends.
What?
You handled his highness's memorial program very well,
a little too weepy from my taste but...
Yes,well the masses tend to like tear-jerker,your excellency.
Spoken like a true TV-man. Still I have to acknowledge to finesse you've shown.
You did well in short time you had.
One would almost think you were expecting His Highness to meet his untimely end.
It's quite common from memorial program to be set in advance for important people.
Does that including me as well?
Recent event may have bumped you up the list a bit your excellency.
I wasn't deemed important enough till now is that it?
How forth right of you!
I'm afraid so sir.
Every thought of this thing,the army could use more memo like you.
I don't think it would be a very good fit. Not really my cup of tea.
You prefer the civil sector I take it. No matter,I have another favor to ask of you.
Tomorrow night Suzaku Kururugi will be transfered to his court martial.
We should line a road with good patriotic Britannians.
Excellent. You catch on quickly don't you?
Be sure the rabble can see his face.
Lord Jeremiah,there are those among the Elevens who see private Kururugi as a hero.
Some might very well make an attempt to free him.
I'll be there personally aboard my Sutherland.
If anyone think of causing trouble,they will be executed on the spot.
Attention all passengers if you become aware of any suspicious items on board,
please alert mutual personnel by using the nearest inter-telephone.
What now?
Face forward and look to your right.
What do you see?
The Britannian city.
It was stolen away from us and built on our sacrifice.
And on the left?
I see our city.
Remnants of the desiccated city after the Britannian sucked it dry.
Good answer.
Now make your way to the front of the train.
The next stop is Okubo. Okubo is next.
Those wishing to transfer to the Chuo-Soubu line should exit at the next stop.
Okubo will be next.
Once again. Those wishing to transfer to the Chuo-Soubu line should exit at the next stop.
Was it you? On the phone?
Wow... Do you think it's a trap?
Well,was that you in Shinjuku? Was that cease fire your doing?
Hey,we're talking to you.
What do you think of my tour at the settlement?
Your tour?
Come-on,there is no way it was this joker.
I wanted you to fully grasp the two,the settlement and the ghetto.
Yeah,we know. There is a difference between us and them.
A very harsh one.
And that's why we resist them.
You are wrong.
Britannia will not fall to terrorism.
Fall?
It's a little bit better than childish nuisance.
What was that?
You call us a bunch of kids?
You should know your enemy. It is not people,but Britannia itself.
It is a war you must wage,but not only innocent.
Take up your sword! Fight for justice!
Oh please. That's all easy enough to say,isn't it?
Hiding behind that mask...why should we even trust you?
She's right!
Lose the mask!
Right. Are you going to show us your face or not?
Very well,I'll show you.
But rather than my face,bear witness to my power.
If I deliver to you the impossible,
then I might have earned your trust.
He killed the prince of Britannia.
Suzaku Kururugi should be treated as a hero.
Yeah,but he's an honorary Britannian.
Prime minister Kururugi was his father.
So what? The bastard gave up Japan,and people don't know that about him.
The whole Shinjuku business was the work of Kouzuki's group wasn't it?
Yes,sir. They're being led by a man named Ohgi at present.
Has Kururugi's family said anything?
No,sir. They broke contact with him once he joined the military.
Tohdoh,what your thought?
We should not become involved in this public execution.
That's cowardly! You are Tohdoh,the miracle worker right?
There is difference between miracles and foolhardiness.
Congratulations!
Those two you asked me about weren't on the list of casualties.
That's good to hear.
Not much luck on your end though,
you may be getting a trial,but no one is pulling for you certainly.
But the courts are where the truth comes to light.
I expect there'll be more smoke and mirrors than anything.
The truth is scarce of late.
If that's how the world works,then...
...so be it
I've no regret.
{\fnLeviBrush\fs60\b1}CODE GEASS\NLelouch of the Rebellion
Any moment. Any moment now.
It's a sight to see.
The throngs' lining in the route. All of them waiting on bated breath.
Waiting for the accused murderer of Prince Clovis to pass by.
An honorary Britanian and a former Eleven Suzaku Kururugi.
Camera 5 is a little slow. Talk to me,Charles,your team been deployed yet?
What? The studio? Let them wait.
Nothing has been pushed back. Everything is going according to plan.
Here we go.
I,I can see them! They have the suspect!
Suzaku Kururugi is headed this way!
Like clockwork.
Huh,what a circus this is. And now this corrupts any of them.
Murderer! Scum! Damned Eleven! We want our prince back!
This is insane. We know that Suzaku is innocent.
The court deemed our testimony inadmissible. There is nothing we can do.
Yes,but...
Is that altruism or humanitarianism?
This isn't a time for a game of semantics!
Not much else to do?
You know where this case\Nis headed as well as I do.
And we can't contact our\Npatron while he's at the summit.
All we can do\Nis let this whole thing go.
Voices of scorn growing ever louder.
Voices bearing testament to a people's love of their prince.
Raining their judgement down on a terrorist.
Suzaku!
Margrave Jeremiah,
integral in settling this case,will be presiding over the trial as acting council.
No way the three even could pull this up on their own.
He told us. He said he'd make the impossible possible.
He gave us his word to save Suzaku Kururugi.
Right. No need to turn back. The die is cast.
Acting council Jeremiah.Jeremiah:
What is it?
Vehicle approaching the main highway from third.
We just let it through as you instructed but...
Do you believe the target could be a terrorist's vehicle?
Well Sir,it's Prince Clovis' car.
The prince's car?
Well looks like we've got a comedian.
Don't worry about it. Just let them through to us.
All forces hold here!
Hey,they stopped. They really did!
Huh! It's just a coincidence.
Yeah,but he said Jeremiah would try to hog all the limelight,make some sort of stand about it.
COINCIDENCE!
This is not a scheduled stop.
Could there have been some sort of accident?
This is site 5. There is a vehicle approaching them.
It's,it's Prince Clovis' personal transport!
And it's heading straight for the cavalcade!
What a... It's straight forward. What is he planning?
Hope they can't tell it's fake.
I see. Just you two then.
I'm sorry. We just need a little more time.
If more people understood what we...
No,the two of you will do just fine.
Huh? Come on! That's ridiculous! There will be too many of them!
With your help,clearing the task at hand will be child's play.
I'll need this by tomorrow.
. All that matters is the exterior.
You dare desecrate His Highness's transport? Come out of there.
I am Zero.
Zero?
Who is this person?
This man calling himself Zero,standing before a full millitary convoy.
What is all this?
What the hell does he think he is doing?
Who is this man calling himself Zero?
Zero? What do you mean,like 'nothing'?
Are we gazing on a terrorist?
Certainly not the wisest if such as the case.
Is he an Eleven?
Now I'll return the favor,Suzaku.
I've seen enough,Zero. This little show of yours is over.
First things first. Why don't you lose that mask?
What in the...!?
Jeremiah,be careful,he's got the...
Yes,Jeremiah.
You never saw inside this thing.
So you assume it holds poison gas.
Wait. You don't understand...
Can all of you watching at home see this?
It's some sort of device,although its purpose is unclear.
Stay with us and we'll see if this so-called terrorist has anything to say.
You bastard!
He's taken every Britannian here hostage,
and he's done it without them even knowing it.
You intend to shoot? I think you know full well what will happen if you do.
Unit 6 bring up the sound and get that camera right in his face!
Sir,it's too "hairy" out here.
Damn,amatures!
Fine,what are your demands?
An exchange. This,for Kururugi.
Like hell.
He's charged with high treason for murdering a prince.
I can't hand him over.
No. You're mistaken,Jeremiah.
He's no murderer.
The man who killed Clovis was myself.
Unbelievable!
The real culprit,hey.
What? What does this mean?
This masked man called Zero - no,we can’t be sure who he is...
...but in any case,he claims to be the real assassin?
So where does this leave the current suspect,Private Kururugi?
How Crap! There is no way out of this.
We are so screwed.
For a single Eleven,you'll save scores of precious Britannians.
I find that to be a bargain.
This is all one big performance to him.
He is mad,I tell you.
Disguising its truck as his highness??
He’ll pay the price for mocking the crown!
Careful. You don't wish the public to learn of Orange,do you?
Orange? What's he talking about?
I don't know.
If I die,it'll all go public. If you don't want that to happen...
What are you talking about? What is this?
You'll do everything in your power to let us go,your prisoner as well.
Right,understood.
You there,release the prisoner.
Eh!?
What on earth are you doing,My Lord?
Get that man over here.
Hah?
Should we? But ...
Hand him over. Nobody gets in his way.
No. What are you thinking? You can't do this!
Lord Kewell,this is an order.
It's hard to tell what's happening from here,
but it seems that Kururugi's release has been broken!
So,who the hell are you?
As I thought,they didn't allow you to speak.
If they get away,we'll lose everything.
It's time to go,Zero.
Well then,tell next time.
You cowardly Eleven. Lord Jeremiah,what are you ...?
You heard me! Stand down now!
They are not alone at all. They jumped right off.
Hit! It worked! Now we can...
Are you imbecile!? There’s nowhere for you to run!
Lord Kewell!
Are you going to follow orders or not?
And believe me,there will be repercussions.
All units,do I make myself clear?
Do everything in your power to help them get away.
Man,I didn't really think he could do it.
Yeah,who is this guy?
That's crap! How many times can a bluff like that work,anyway?
You gotta give the guy some credit though.
Huh?
Gotta admit it nobody else could’ve pulled that off.
Not the Japanese Liberation Front,certainly not me.
We’ve always thought that a full-on war with Britannian wasn’t a possibility at all.
But maybe with him,it is.
It looks like they treated you rather roughly.
Now you know what they're really like,Private Kururugi.
Britannia is rotten.
If you wish to bring change to this world,then join me.
So,is it true? Are you really the one who killed Prince Clovis?
This is war.
Why wouldn't I kill an enemy commander?
And the gas? Those were civilians out there.
A bluff to help things along.
The result,not a single death.
The result? That's all that matters to you,I suppose. Huh...
Come join me.
The Britannia you serve is a worthless dominion.
Maybe that's true,but...
...but this nation,it can be changed for the better,and from within.
Changed?
And any ends gained through contemptible means aren't worth anything.
Wait. Where are you going?
My court-martial begins in an hour.
Damn,are you mad?
The only reason they're giving you a trial is to find you guilty.
The judge,the prosecution,and defense.
Rules are rules.
And if I don't go,they start to cracking down on Elevens and honorary Britannians.
But you'll die.
I don't mind.
Don't be an idiot.
An old friend of mine always used to tell me that. He'd say I was a fool.
It's my weakness,I guess.
I'd try to bring you in,but you'd just end up killing me.
And If I'm going to die,it'll be in the service of the people.
Even so,I thank you...
...for saving me.
You fool.
Yes,apparently. Private Kururugi has made contact with the authorities.
It would seem the Zero has released him.
However now that the original charge against Eleven is thrown into a question,
it's very possible Kururugi would be found innocent and acquitted.
Thank goodness.
For things in perspective on all of this,we now turn to our leader analyst ...
Miss Sayoko?
{\fade(255,0,255,0,500,5500,8000)}Subtitle: Willing
Yukedomo kemonomichi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Walking along the animal path
Shishi yotorayoto hoe\N{\c&H00FF00&}Roaring with the lions and tigers
Akane sasu sora no kanata ni mahoroba\N{\c&H00FF00&}Paradise lying far across a sky dyed red
Yuushuu no kodoku ni samayou seishun wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}To a youth wandering,imprisoned in loneliness
Yowasato ikari ga sugata naki teki desu ka\N{\c&H00FF00&}Are weakness and hatred shapeless enemies?
Chichi yo madaware wa\N{\c&H00FF00&}Oh father,I am still...
Onore wo shirigatashi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Learning who I am
Sakidatsu anira no\N{\c&H00FF00&}As I pursue the backs I no longer see
Mienai senakawo oeba\N{\c&H00FF00&}Of the elder brothers who have gone before me
Mayoi no hitoyo ni\N{\c&H00FF00&}In the night I spend lost
Myoujou wa izanau\N{\c&H00FF00&}The morning star beckons to me
Shi shite owaranu\N{\c&H00FF00&}This will not end in my death
Yume wo kogaredomo\N{\c&H00FF00&}I long for my dream
Tashika na kimi kosowaga inochi\N{\c&H00FF00&}My faith in you sustains my life
Reppu no kouya de\N{\c&H00FF00&}In the windswept wilderness
Chou yo hanayoto iki\N{\c&H00FF00&}Living with the butterflies and flowers
Tokoshie no haru ni sakisou maboroshi\N{\c&H00FF00&}Blooming together in a mirage of eternal Spring
Kondaku nojunketsu\N{\c&H00FF00&}If my purity seems muddied
Kono mi wayogoretemo\N{\c&H00FF00&}And my body seems filthy
Kokoro no nishiki wo shinjiteite kudasai\N{\c&H00FF00&}Please believe in the finery within my heart
Hahayo kesshite ware wa namidawo misene domo\N{\c&H00FF00&}Oh mother,I will show no tears
Ashimoto no\N{\c&H00FF00&}They vanish like...
Kusa ni tsuyu wa kiemosede\N{\c&H00FF00&}The dew in the grass beneath my feet
So naive!
I was sure Suzaku would understand.
Change the system from within?
Ridiculous! The system will just swallow him up! It’ll eat him alive!
I can’t beg for their charity to live my life!
I just can’t.
I won’t live by their rules anymore!
{\fs65\pos(960,680)}The Princess and The Witch

